Guide to the W. D. Davies papers, 1911-2007 UA.29.02.0016
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2014.0065, 1911-2007; 2
  - Books, 5
    - The Works of Flavius Josephus (Box 64)
      Author: William Whiston; Place of Publication: Edinburgh; Hardcover; Language: English; Translated by William Whiston; Significance to W.D. Davies: Annotated
    - The Works of Flavius Josephus, 1906 (Box 74)
      Author: William Whiston, edited by D.S. Margoliouth; Publisher: George Routledge and Sons Ltd.; Place of Publication: London Language: English
    - The World Crisis: 1911-1918 (Box 71)
      Author: Winston Churchill; Publisher: Odhams Press LTD; Place of Publication: London; Hardcover; Language: English
    - Y Cawg Aur, 1928 (Box 72)
      Author: Iowerth Cyfeiliog Peate; Place of Publication: London; Hardcover; Language: Welsh
    - Y Cawr Awenydd, 1990 (Box 69)
      Author: R.S. Thomas; Publisher: Gomer Press; Place of Publication: Llandysul; Hardcover; Language: Welsh; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Y Coed, 1969 (Box 69)
      Author: Gwenallt; Publisher: Gomer Press; Place of Publication: Llandysul; Hardcover; Language: Welsh; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Y Ddolen, 1946 (Box 69)
      Author: Chweched Llyfr Anrheg; Hardcover; Language: Welsh; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Y Flodeugerdd Gymraeg, 1931 (Box 69)
      Author: W.J. Gruffydd; Publisher: University of Wales Press; Place of Publication: Cardiff; Hardcover; Language: Welsh; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Y Flodeugerdd Gymraeg, 1931 (Box 69)
      Author: W.J. Gruffydd; Publisher: University of Wales Press; Place of Publication: Cardiff; Hardcover; Language: Welsh; Significance to W.D. Davies: belonged to Mary Llewelyn, Eurwen L. Davies' sister.
    - Y Llwybrau Gynt, 1971 (Box 69)
      Author: Alun Oldfield-Davies; Publisher: Gomer Press; Place of Publication: Llandysul; Hardcover; Language: Welsh
    - Y Tadau An Bynnol, 1898 (Box 72)
      Author: Parch John Davies, Parch W.I Morris; Publisher: Welsh National Press Company; Place of Publication: Caernafron; paperback; Language: Welsh
    - Y Testament Newydd Cymraeg, 1976 (Box 72)
      Author: Isaac Thomas; Publisher: Wales University Press; Place of Publication: Wales; Hardcover; Language: Welsh
    - Y Traethodydd, 2001 (Box 69)
      Author: Unknown; Paperback; Language: Welsh; Significance to W.D. Davies: Memorial
    - The Yeshiva (Box 74)
      Author: Chaim Grade; Language: English
    - The Yeshiva: Volume II, 1977 (Box 70)
      Author: Chaim Grade; Publisher: Bobbs Merrill Company, Inc.; Place of Publication: United States; Hardcover; Language: English
    - Ym Mhob Pen Ysgrifau, 1948 (Box 72)
      Author: Iowerth C. Peate; Publisher: Aberystwyth Press; Place of Publication: Llandysul; Hardcover; Language: Welsh
    - Ynys Yr Hud, 1923 (Box 69)
      Author: W.J. Gruffydd; Publisher: The Educational Publishing; Place of Publication: Cardiff; Hardcover; Language: Welsh; Significance to W.D. Davies: Inscription
    - Yorkshire United Independent College (Box 74)
      Author: K.W. Wadsworth; Language: English; Significance to W.D. Davies: cited in text.
    - yr awdl a'r bryddest, 1937 (Box 72)
      Author: Unknown; Publisher: Bwyllgor Eisteddfod Genedlaethol; Place of Publication: Machynlleth; Paperback; Language: Welsh
    - Zohar: The Book of Splendor, 1963 (Box 75)
      Author: Gershom G. Scholem; Publisher: Schoken Books; Place of Publication: New York; Hardcover; Language: English